eatwell101.com 2019-12-24

# 1“ — Eatwell101

**Editorial Policy  
** Eatwell 101’s recommendations are selected by our editorial staff and trusted contributors.  
Most important, our taste is not for sale. Brands and establishments cannot pay to be recommended by Eatwell 101. Our sponsors and advertisers are featured in obvious positions on our website and emails, because we believe your trust is essential to our success.

If you’re a business owner or publicist or just an ardent fan of a local establishment, a brand or a website, you can suggest it to our editors. See our Contact page for information by clicking [here](http://www.eatwell101.com/contact-us).

**Tip/Advertorial Email  
** Occasionally we’ll send you a Partner Tip email from one of our advertisers. These advertorial features are clearly marked as such by the email’s subject line and a note at the top of the article itself. The content of these Partner Tips is paid for by our sponsors, and does not reflect the opinions of the Eatwell 101 editorial staff.

**Privacy Policy**  
Eatwell101.com is committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This privacy policy tells you about the information we collect on our website and how we use that information. By using the Eatwell101.com website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy policy, which may be modified from time to time by us.

**Children Under 13:**  
We care about protecting the privacy of children. We won’t knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personally identifying information. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. If you’re under 13, please do not provide us with any personally identifying information (such as your name, your email address or your phone number).

### **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act):**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

WE DO NOT SPECIFICALLY MARKET TO CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13 YEARS OLD.

**Information We Collect:**  
The information we gather falls into two categories: (1) information you supply when you register to receive emails or comment on the website, and (2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our site.

**Personally Identifying Information**  
In operating the Site, Eatwell101.com may include registration, comment forms, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, e-mail addresses, and other contact information.

### Tracking Information

**Cookies.**  
From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Web site. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on our website other than cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Web site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

**Click Tracking.**  
As is true of most websites, Eatwell101.com gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Except as noted herein, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information.

**IP Addresses.**  
Each user’s IP address is logged with each visit and each action performed on Eatwell101.com. This information is never provided to the third parties, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, and is logged only for a temporary period of time. IP address information is linked to personal information and may be used in an effort to block a “banned” user from accessing the Site.

**Advertising.**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Notice Regarding Online behavioural Advertising**  
We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clickedor scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide  
advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

**Participation on a Public Website.**  
You should be aware that any personal information you submit on Eatwell101.com in the comments may be read, collected, or used by other users of this Site, including anonymous visitors.

### How Your Information Will Be Used:

**Personal Information**  
We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify your identity, to check your qualifications, or to follow up with transactions initiated on the site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to Eatwell101.com, or to send you additional information about Eatwell101.com.

**Anonymous Information**  
We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

**Use of Cookies**  
We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**  
We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Eatwell101.com, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Eatwell101.com or the users of this site, or (3) act under circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of this site.

**Security**  
Eatwell101.com has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

**Comments**  
Eatwell101.com may include interactive forms such as comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Third Party Websites**  
Eatwell101.com may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

### **Your California Privacy Rights**

Residents of California may request a list of third parties to which certain personal information (as defined by applicable California law) obtained through a Digital Service was disclosed by Reach Media Inc. during the preceding year for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please contact us at:

Reach Media Group atn “Your California Privacy Rights”  
1330 Avenue of the Americas  
Suite #23A  
New York, NY 10019

For all requests, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. In your request, you need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please also indicate in your request the name of the Digital Service to which your request applies. Please note that we will NOT accept requests via the telephone, email, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

### **European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at hello AT eatwell101 DOT com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

If you are a resident of a country in the EEA, you have the rights, among others, to:

  * (i) access your personal data
  * (ii) ensure the accuracy of your personal data
  * (iii) the right to have us delete your personal data
  * (iv) the right to restrict further processing of your personal data, and
  * (v) the right to complain to a supervisory authority in your country of residence in the event that data is misused

If you believe that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us addressed to the following:

Reach Media Group atn EU Privacy Complaints  
1330 Avenue of the Americas  
Suite #23A  
New York, NY 10019

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this policy, our practices related to this site, please feel contact us at the following hello AT eatwell101 DOT com.

**Updates and Changes**  
We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this privacy policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on Eatwell101.com and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site. It is your responsibility to review this privacy policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.

This policy was last updated on September 12, 2018.
